Guide to the Benoit Mandelbrot Papers M1857
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 9. Working files/Research, circa 1948-2000s
  - Working Files - handwritten notes and calculations, circa 1990s (Box 145, Folders 8-10)
  - Working Files - handwritten notes and calculations, circa 1990s (Box 146, Folders 1-5)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files, 1990s (Box 428, Folders 1-7)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files, 1990s (Box 429, Folders 1-17)
  - Working Files - edited manuscript drafts/partial drafts, notes, clippings, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Working Files - newspaper/magazine clippings, reprints/photocopies of articles by others, partial manuscripts, handwritten notes, 1990s-2000s (Box 82, Folders 7-11)
  - Working Files - newspaper/magazine clippings, reprints/photocopies of articles by others, partial manuscripts, handwritten notes, 1990s-2000s (Box 83, Folders 1-3)
  - Working Files - newspaper/magazine clippings, reprints/photocopies of articles by others, web article/website printouts, handwritten notes, 1990s-2000s (Box 83, Folders 4-5)
  - Working Files - newspaper/magazine clippings, reprints/photocopies of articles by others, web article/website printouts, handwritten notes, 1990s-2000s (Box 84, Folders 1-5)
  - Working Files - newspaper/magazine clippings, reprints/photocopies of articles by others, web article/website printouts, handwritten notes, 1990s-2000s (Box 85, Folders 1-5)
  - Working Files - web/newspaper/magazine clippings, 1990s-2000s (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Working Files - correspondence, handwritten notes, newspaper/magazine clippings, flyers, articles by others, 1990s-2000s (Box 202, Folders 4-6)
  - Working Files - correspondence, handwritten notes, newspaper/magazine clippings, flyers, articles by others, 1990s-2000s (Box 199, Folders 1-6)
  - Working Files - handwritten notes, partial manuscript drafts, correspondence, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 30, Folders 5-6)
  - Working Files - articles by others, newspaper/magazine clippings, notes, correspondence, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 201, Folders 4-7)
  - Working Files - articles by others, newspaper/magazine clippings, notes, correspondence, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 202, Folders 1-3)
  - Working Files - writings; drafts; articles by others; clippings; handwritten notes, 1990s-2010 (Box 147, Folders 2-3)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files, 1990s-2000s (Box 424, Folders 1-15)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files, 1990s-2000s (Box 425, Folders 1-15)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files, 1990s-2000s (Box 430, Folders 1-12)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files, 1990s-2000s (Box 431, Folders 1-16)
  - Working Files - article drafts/partial drafts (edited), circa early 2000s (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Working Files - article drafts/partial drafts (edited); correspondence; handwritten notes, circa early 2000s (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Working Files - article drafts/partial drafts (edited); correspondence; newspaper clippings; reprints by others; handwritten notes etc., circa 2000-2005 (Box 71, Folders 2-6)
  - Working Files - article drafts/partial drafts (edited); correspondence; newspaper clippings; reprints by others; handwritten notes etc., circa 2000-2005 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - article drafts - miscellaneous edited manuscript and computer printouts, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Working Files - miscellaneous edited manuscript and computer printout drafts, correspondence, c. 2002-2005 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Working Files - miscellaneous edited manuscript and computer printout drafts, correspondence, c. 2002-2005 (Box 48, Folders 1-4)
  - Working Files - miscellaneous edited manuscript and computer printout drafts, correspondence, c. 2003-2006 (Box 48, Folders 5-6)
  - Working Files - article drafts/partial drafts (edited); correspondence; articles by others; book reviews, 2006-2007 (Box 72, Folders 4-6)
  - Working Files - handwritten notes, web article printouts, articles by others, business cards, miscellaneous article/chapter drafts by BBM, circa 2008-2009 (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - Working Files - Reprints/web printouts of articles by others on social network analysis and linked data (some annotated), 2009-2011 (Box 56, Folders 5-6)
  - Working Files - Reprints/web printouts of articles by others on social network analysis and linked data (some annotated), 2009-2011 (Box 57, Folders 1-4)
  - Working Files - internet article printouts, news clippings, reprints by others, handwritten notes (from box on floor of BBM's apartment office), circa 2000s (Box 80, Folders 8-10)
  - Working Files - internet article printouts, news clippings, reprints by others, handwritten notes (from box on floor of BBM's apartment office), circa 2000s (Box 81, Folders 1-3)
  - Working Files - articles by others; newspaper/magazine clippings; event/conference announcements; web article printouts, 2000s (Box 147, Folders 7-8)
  - Working Files - articles by others; newspaper/magazine clippings; event/conference announcements; web article printouts, 2000s (Box 148, Folders 1-7)
  - Working Files - articles by others; newspaper/magazine clippings; event/conference announcements; web article printouts, 2000s (Box 149, Folders 1-7)
  - Working Files - articles by others; newspaper/magazine clippings; event/conference announcements; web article printouts, 2000s (Box 150, Folders 1-4)
  - Working Files - miscellaneous forms, article printouts, 2000s (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - Working Files - working notes (handwritten), circa 2000s (Box 150, Folders 5-8)
  - Working Files - handwritten drafts, notes, circa 2000s (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Working Files - manuscripts in progress - Given/Mandelbrot - R/S theorems/file and misc. seed stuff, undated (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Working Files - long run EGN, undated (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Working Files - self affinity, undated (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - spectra, undated (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Working Files - trema, undated (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Working Files - Trumball Transparencies (photocopy), undated (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Working Files - the zero crossing problem, undated (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Working Files - misc. notes/printouts, undated (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Working Files - Scientific notes, undated (on BBM's desktop at IBM 2010 Nov) (Box 213, Folders 5-6)
  - Working Files - "Non-G, Non-E Mess" [Non-Gaussian, Non-Euclidean] (heavily edited drafts, notes) (Box 216, Folder 9)
  - Working Files - "Very erratic chance fluctuations and statistical self similarity" [draft for presentation?], undated (Box 216, Folder 8)
  - Working Files - "R/S miscellany" undated (Box 216, Folder 10)
  - Working files - Notebook; equations and notes, undated (Box 500, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - miscellaneous (Box 216, Folder 11)
  - Working files - baying-and-holding, undated (Box 314, Folder 3)
  - Working files - "Jakobon paper, revised," undated (Box 314, Folder 4)
  - Working files - "Latane Fischer," undated (Box 314, Folder 5)
  - Working files - "Non-Euclidian," undated (Box 314, Folder 6)
  - Working files - Siebel - words, undated (Box 314, Folder 7)
  - Working files - Speculation and stop-loss procedures, undated (Box 314, Folder 8)
  - Working files - unlabeled folder of scientific notes, undated (Box 314, Folder 9)
  - Working files – IBM research (Box 504, Folders 10)
  - Working files – equation notes (Flat-box 513, Folder 1)
  - Working files – research notes/drafts (Box 504, Folders 3-8)
  - Working files – clippings and miscellaneous papers (Box 504, Folders 1-2)
  - Working files - loose handwritten notes, undated (Box 314, Folder 10)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files (Box 413, Folders 1-13)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files; mostly notes on loose scrap paper (Box 414, Folders 1-14)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files (Box 415, Folders 1-11)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files; mostly magazines, clippings, and reprints (Box 416, Folders 1-11)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files (Box 417, Folders 1-10)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files (Box 418, Folders 1-9)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files (Box 419, Folders 1-13)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files (Box 420, Folders 1-14)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files (Box 421, Folders 1-11)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files (Box 422, Folders 1-16)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files (Box 432, Folders 1-20)
- Series 10. Professional Activities, 1954-2011
  This series consists of materials documenting the professional activities of Mandelbrot, including invited talks, colloquia, conferences, lectures, exhibits and fellowships. Major record types include correspondence, clippings and conference flyers, programs and other ephemera. This series is arranged chronologically.
  - International Congress of Psychology, 1954 (Montreal) (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Lecture notices/programs/flyers/calendars; correspondence, 1954-1970 (on BBM's desktop at IBM as of 2011 Feb 4) (Box 159, Folders 2-4)
  - Misc travel/conferences, 1950s (Box 230, Folder 1)
  - New York Section IEEE Annual Fellows Awards Dinner, 1960 Feb 14 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - UNESCO conference, 1960 (Box 230, Folder 2)
  - Third Prague Conference on Information Theory, 1962 (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - "Le Concept d'Information dans la Science Contemporaine" - Paris, 1962 (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - Kyoto 1966 (correspondence, travel planning, receipts) (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Misc travel/conferences, 1960s (Box 230, Folder 3)
  - "Princeton '71" [transparencies for a presentation/lecture?], circa 1971 (Box 230, Folder 4)
  - Australia, 1978 (Box 461, Folder 1)
  - College de France (invitations), 1979 Jan-Feb (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - "Trumbull/College de France - transparencies" circa 1970s (Box 230, Folder 5)
  - Sigma XI, 1980-1982 (Box 466, Folder 1)
  - Fractal talks, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - L. F. Richardson Centerary Lecture - Paisley College of Technology, Scotland, 1982 May 19 (Box 230, Folder 6)
  - IBM Europe Insitute - Fractals: Theory and Applicaitons, Courchevel, France, 1982 Jul 18-24 (BBM was principal organizer) (Box 193, Folders 1-4)
  - Fractal meetings, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - IBM Europe Institute 1982 - Workshop on Fractals, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - International Statistics Institute, 1982-1987 (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - David Marr Conference - MIT, 1983 Apr 24-29 (Box 230, Folder 7)
  - IMA Symposium on "Fractals: Fractional Dimensions and their Applications" - London, 1983 Jun 8 (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Cyril S. Smith 80th Birthday Symposium on Structure, 1983 Oct 4 (Box 230, Folder 8)
  - "Fractals: How to imitate the mountains and the clouds and to create wild and beautiful new shapes" - New York Academy of Sciences, 1983 Nov 18 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Third Conference on Fractals - "Fractals in the Physical Sciences" - Gaithersburg, MD, 1983 Nov 21-23 (Box 230, Folder 9)
  - Third Conference on Fractals in the Physical Sciences 1983 Nov 21-23 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Third Conference on Fractals - "Fractals in the Physical Sciences" - Gaithersburg, Maryland, 1983 Nov 21-23 (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - Third Conference on Fractals, 1983 (Box 459, Folder 1)
  - Fractals in the Physical Sciences - Maryland, 1983 Nov 21-23 (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - Fractals meetings, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Cornell (Beverly West), 1983 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Edinburgh - Statphys Conference, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Japan, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - Fractal talks, 1983 (Box 193, Folder 8)
  - NVAG Workshop - Lovejoy, Montreal, 1983 (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Creation et creativite - Centre d'Art Contemporain, Universite de Geneve, 1984 Jan 3 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - 14th Conference on Stochastic Processes and their Applications - Gothenburg, Sweden, 1984 Jun 12-16 (Box 193, Folder 10)
  - Nobel Symposium 59 - "The physics of chaos and related problems" - Sweden, 1984 Jun 11-16 (Box 230, Folder 12)
  - Symposium fur Theoretische Chemie in Emmetten/Schweiz, 1984 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Fractal meetings, 1984 (Box 87, Folders 12-13)
  - Materials Research Society 1984 Fall Meeting (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Les Houches, 1984 (Box 193, Folders 11-13)
  - Leon Lectures, University of Pennsylvania, 1984 (Box 193, Folder 14)
  - Bruxelles, 1984 (Box 193, Folder 15)
  - T.E.D. Conference - Monterey CA, 1984 (Box 230, Folder 13)
  - Misc travel/conferences, 1984 (Box 230, Folders 10-11)
  - 6th Trieste International Symposium "Fractals in Phyiscs" - program and abstracts, 1985 Jul 9-12 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - American Mathematical Society Meeting - Laramie, Wyoming, 1985 Aug 10-15 (Box 193, Folder 16)
  - Niels Bohr Centennial Symposium, 1985 Nov 12-14 (Box 159, Folder 10)
  - Gordon Research Conference 1985 (BBM conference chairperson) - correspondence, registration cards, preliminary programs, applications, flyers (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Gordon Research Conference 1985 (BBM conference chairperson) - correspondence, registration cards, preliminary programs, applications, flyers (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Fractal meetings, 1985 (Box 88, Folders 2-3)
  - Materials Research Society 1985 Fall Meeting (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Gordon Research Conference, 1985 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Fractal talks, 1985 (Box 193, Folder 17)
  - Bremen, 1985 (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - SIAM, 1985 (Box 461, Folder 10)
  - Misc travel/conferences, 1985 (Box 230, Folders 14-16)
  - Mathematical Research Institute, Oberwolfach, 1985-1987 (Box 230, Folder 17)
  - Professional Development Seminars Spring 1986 - "Fractals: Basic Concepts, Computation and Rendering" - Framingham State College, 1986 May 3 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - IBM Europe Institute - Oberlich, Austria - program, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Gordon Research Conference (participant lists, programs, correspondence), 1986 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Materials Research Society 1986 Fall Meeting (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - IBM Europe Institute - Oberlech, Austria, 1986 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Oberlech, 1986 (IBM Europe Institute) (Box 194, Folders 2-3)
  - Goethe House, New York German Cultural Center, 1986 (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - "Dynamics on fractals and hierarchies of critical exponents" - Orsay, France, 1986 Sep-Oct (Box 230, Folder 18)
  - Symposium U - Fractal Aspects of Materials, 1986 Dec 2-4 (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - Misc travel/conferences, 1986 (Box 230, Folder 19)
  - Poland, 1986 (Box 231, Folder 1)
  - Meetings, 1986 (Box 231, Folder 2)
  - Boston University - Boston Colloquium for the Philosophy of Science, 1986-1987 (Box 194, Folder 5)
  - Werner Heisenberg Lectures - Bavairan Academy of Sciences, 1986-1987 (Box 194, Folder 6)
  - Franklin Institute, 1986-1989 (Box 194, Folder 7)
  - Problemes Nonlineaires Appliques - Ensembles Fractals - INRIA, 1987 Jan 12-15 (Box 194, Folder 8)
  - MAA program (invited talk) 1987 Jan 22 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Computer Graphics in the Arts and Sciences - NYU, 1987 Jun 11 (Box 231, Folder 3)
  - Colloque Paul Levy - Palaiseau (France), 1987 Jun 22-26 (Box 159, Folder 12)
  - The First JUST (Japan and U.S. Transcultural) Seminar at Lake Tazawa, 1987 Jul 26 - Aug 1 (Box 159, Folder 13)
  - Materials Research Society 1987 Fall Meeting - Boston (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - "Dynamic Patterns in Complex Systems" Conference - Ft. Lauderdale, Florida, 1987 Oct 21-23 (Box 194, Folder 9)
  - Boston University Commencement, 1987 (Box 194, Folder 10)
  - Boston Museum of Science (MIT), 1987 (Box 194, Folder 11)
  - Ars Electronica - Linz/Austria, 1987 (Box 194, Folder 12)
  - Goethe Institute - Toronto, 1987 (Box 194, Folder 13)
  - Lund University, 1987 (Box 194, Folder 14)
  - Barcelona, 1987 (Box 194, Folder 15)
  - Institute of Theoretical Physics - Academia Sinica, Beijing, China, 1987 (Box 194, Folder 16)
  - CESTA, 1987 (Box 195, Folder 1)
  - Cincinnati, 1987 (Box 195, Folder 2)
  - Cornell, 1987 (Box 195, Folder 3)
  - Hungary, 1987 (Box 195, Folder 4)
  - Misc conferences/travel, 1987 (Box 231, Folder 4)
  - Portuguese Conference on Fractals - Lisbon, 1987-1988 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Special Seminar - Erice, Sicily, 1988 (Box 303, Folder 1)
  - MASSCOMP, 1988 Mar 12 (Box 231, Folder 9)
  - National Academy of Sciences 125th Annual Meeting, 1988 Apr 24-27 (Box 231, Folder 6)
  - Goodyear Symposium, 1988 Apr (Box 195, Folder 5)
  - Landau Memorial Conference, Tel Aviv, 1988 Jun 6-10 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - 17th Conference on Mathematical Geophysics - Blanes (Costa Brava, Spain), 1988 Jun 20-25 (Box 195, Folder 6)
  - Symposium and exhibition - "Fractals and Computed Art" - TU Delft, 1988 Jul 1 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - 1988 Bea Halley Ross Lectures - Ohio State University, 1988 Aug (Box 231, Folder 5)
  - New York Academy of Science - Science Research Training Program, 1988 Fall (Box 231, Folder 10)
  - Materials Research Society 1988 Fall Meeting (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Centenaire de Szolem Mandelbrot - Universite de Paris, 1988 Dec (Box 195, Folder 7)
  - Gordon Research Conference on fractals (schedule, participants, correspondence), 1988 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Kaos Foundation "Chaos" exhibition symposium, 1988 (Box 238, Folder 4)
  - Caltech - Distinguished Alumni Award, 1988 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Cornell University, 1988 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Delft - Ultrecht, 1988 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Informatik - Symposium at Cologne, 1988 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Choate, Wesleyan, 1988 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - NATO ASI "Fluctuations and Pattern Formations" Cargese, 1988 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Connecticut University, 1988 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Geological Society of America - Denver, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - French Press Tour, 1988 (Box 195, Folder 8)
  - Pace University, 1988 (Box 231, Folder 7)
  - Institute of Physics of the National Autonomous University of Mexico 50th Anniversary, 1988 (Box 231, Folder 8)
  - Exhibition - "Frontiers of Chaos: Computer Graphics Face Complex Dynamics" - H.-O. Peitgen and P.H. Richter, 1988-1989 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - Japan-US (JAMS) Seminars, 1988-1990 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - Nobel Conference - Gustavus Adolphus College, 1988-1993 (Box 195, Folder 9)
  - "Science and the Unexpected" - IBM United Kingdom, 1989 Mar 9-10 (Box 195, Folder 10)
  - "Think: Innovation at IBM," 1989 Sep 19 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - "The Fractal Cosmos" - Lecture at the Smithsonian, 1989 Oct 20 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - "A World of Fractals" lecture - Marist College, 1989 Nov 15 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - American Institute of Graphic Arts (AIGA) Conference, New York, 1989 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - New Museum of Contemporary Art - "Strange Attractors: Signs of Chaos," 1989 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Australia travel, 1989 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Materials Research Society 1989 Fall Meeting (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Freiburg, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 11)
  - IBM, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 12)
  - Geometrie fractale et analyse - University of Montreal, 1989 (Box 231, Folder 11)
  - Statphys, 1989 (Box 459, Folders 4-5)
  - ARTEC, Nagoya City, Japan, 1989-1990 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - IBM articles/clippings, 1980s (Box 459, Folder 6)
  - IBM Fellows - reports, 1980s (Box 459, Folders 7-9)
  - Misc travel/conferences, 1980s (Box 231, Folder 12)
  - Switzerland, invitations – circa 1980s (Box 461, Folder 2)
  - ACM SIGGRAPH; includes conference programs, correspondence, presentation drafts and notes, circa 1981-1991 (Box 460, Folders 1-11)
  - Salisbury State College, 1983 (Box 461, Folder 3)
  - Warsaw, 1983 (Box 461, Folder 4)
  - Trieste Symposium, 1984 (Box 461, Folders 6-7)
  - Vancouver, 1984 (Box 461, Folder 8)
  - AMS, fractal geometry sessions - circa 1984-1985 (Box 461, Folder 5)
  - Penn State, 1985 (Box 461, Folder 9)
  - Tel Aviv, 1985 (Box 461, Folder 11)
  - AGU, 1986 (Box 462, Folder 2)
  - Aspenas, 1986 (Box 462, Folder 3)
  - SUNY Albany, 1986 (Box 462, Folder 1)
  - Roussel, 1986 (Box 462, Folder 4)
  - Saint John's College, 1986 (Box 462, Folder 5)
  - UC Santa Cruz, 1986-1987 (Box 462, Folder 6)
  - Sudbury, 1986 (Box 462, Folder 7)
  - Syracuse University, 1986 (Box 462, Folder 8)
  - Tashkent, 1986 (Box 462, Folder 9)
  - University of Washington, 1986 (Box 462, Folder 10)
  - AGU, 1987 (Box 462, Folder 11)
  - APS, Certificate of Fellowship, 1987 (Box 466, Folder 2)
  - SUNY Purchase, 1987 (Box 462, Folder 12)
  - Rome, 1987 (Box 462, Folder 13)
  - Saint John's Cathedral - fractal exhibit, 1987-1988 (Box 463, Folder 1)
  - University of Virginia, 1987 (Box 463, Folder 2)
  - University of Alberta, 1988 (Box 463, Folder 3)
  - AMS, 1988 (Box 463, Folder 4)
  - University of Arkansas, 1988 (Box 463, Folder 5)
  - Princeton, Supercomputer Center, 1988 (Box 463, Folder 6)
  - Rome, 1988 (Box 463, Folder 7)
  - Royal Society, 1988 (Box 463, Folder 8)
  - Science and the Arts Symposium, 1988 (Box 463, Folder 9)
  - Trieste, 1988 (Box 463, Folder 10)
  - Union College, 1988-1989 (Box 463, Folder 11)
  - Wall Street Seminar, 1988 (Box 463, Folder 12)
  - Fractal conferences, Germany, 1988-1994 (Box 501, Folder 1)
  - AIP (Woods Hole), 1989-1990 (Box 464, Folder 1)
  - Russia, 1989 (Box 464, Folder 2)
  - Gunther Stent party, 1989 (Box 464, Folder 3)
  - Trieste, 1989 (Box 464, Folder 4)
  - Gordon Research Conference - Fractals (flyers, programs, correspondence), 1990 Aug 6-10 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Gustavus Adolphus College Nobel Conference XXVI (brochures, correspondence, clippings, programs, name tags), 1990 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Desert Research Institute Nevada Medal (correspondence, reprints, programs, agendas, pamphlets, clippings), 1990-1993 (Box 89, Folders 10-11)
  - Hunter College lecture, 1990 Apr 4 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Guggenheim - "New York Notes: Music and Fractals," 1990 Apr 19-20 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Cherwell-Simon lecture, Oxford, 1990 May 18 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - University of Warwick colloquia, 1990 May 24 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - IBM Germany International Symposium on Fractlas, 1990 May (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Fractal 90 - Lisbon/Portugal, 1990 Jun 6-8 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Institute for Mathematics and its Applications - University of Minnesota, 1990 Jul 2-27 (Box 231, Folder 13)
  - Fractal 90 conference - Lisbon - conference program, 1990 (Box 140, Folders 3-5)
  - Long Island University - lecture, 1990 Jun 15 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - European Technical Executive Forum, La Huelpe, 1990 Jun 19-21 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - "Fractals" lecture, Philips Labs, 1990 Oct 5 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Scotland (Glasgow, Edinburgh), 1990 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Gordon Research Conference on Fractals, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Rouse Ball lectgure, University of Cambridge, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Materials Research Society Fall Meeting 1990 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - The Chamber Music Society of Lincoln Center, Alice Tully Hall - IBM Fractals Project Visuals, 1991 Mar 8 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Connecticut High School Physics Teachers Institute, 1991 Mar 28 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - "Chaos and the Fractal Geometry of Nature" lecture, University of Bath, 1991 May 14 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Conference on Fractal Geometry - Boston University, 1991 Jul 11 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - "Fractals: For the Pleasures of the Eye and the Pleasure of the Mind" lecture, Iona College, 1991 Dec 5 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Lecture, Johns Hopkins University, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - American Association of Petroleum Geologists (AAPG) Annual General Meeting, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - Paris, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Schrodinger Lecture - Imperial College London, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - "Tulle" - Lycee Edmond Perrier, 1991-1996 (Box 231, Folders 14-15)
  - Alpbach, 1992 (Box 464, Folders 6-7)
  - Fractals in Engineering - Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1992 Jun 3-5 (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - Hitchcock Visiting Professor - UC Berkeley, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - Japan and Korea (NTT Forum), 1992 (Box 464, Folders 8-9)
  - National Council of Teachers of Mathematics, Nashville, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 22)